<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>adventure on Misfir3: The Blog</title>
    <link>https://misfir3.org/tags/adventure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in adventure on Misfir3: The Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://misfir3.org/tags/adventure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pioneer 400 Day 3</title>
      <link>https://misfir3.org/post/p400-day3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://misfir3.org/post/p400-day3/</guid>
      <description>Pioneer 400 Day 3 This ended up being my shortest day in time and miles. In my head, I had thought of maybe passing through Idaho Falls, restocking and camping on the way to Lava Hot Springs somewhere &amp;hellip; it sort of made sense to me. That&amp;rsquo;s not how it played out and I believe it was for the better. It was a dry, windy, dusty and warm day.
Sawing Logs vs Logging Operations The night before I had seen the signs about a logging operation, but had not planned on the 5 AM arrival of logging equipment/trucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1 - Pioneer 400</title>
      <link>https://misfir3.org/post/p400-day1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://misfir3.org/post/p400-day1/</guid>
      <description>Day 1 After getting out of the house and driving up to the start, I arrived in Logan around 9 AM. I got changed (Joy Ride bike shop back door was open and someone there let me in to use the bathroom etc). I put my bike up on the stand to lube the chain and got changed. As we&amp;rsquo;ll see later (day 3), I realized I has lost my lube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2 - Pioneer 400</title>
      <link>https://misfir3.org/post/p400-day2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://misfir3.org/post/p400-day2/</guid>
      <description>Day 2 I had planned to get up around 5 AM, figuring that was more or less my body&amp;rsquo;s usual wake up time and having gone to bed 1030 or so, it seemed reasonable. I had gotten up a number of times to pee and hadn&amp;rsquo;t slept well and around 5 I was getting some decent sleep for a few minutes, so I rolled out of the tent officially about 545.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pioneer 400 Trip Overview</title>
      <link>https://misfir3.org/post/p400-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://misfir3.org/post/p400-overview/</guid>
      <description>Pioneer 400 I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to do longer than overnight bikepacking trips, including at least one solo trip. These least 2 years with the pandemic and schedule conflicts with friends I might do bikepacking (or even backpacking trips) with, things have just not worked out. I haven&amp;rsquo;t really had a proper &amp;lsquo;vacation&amp;rsquo; since 2019. And by &amp;lsquo;proper&amp;rsquo;, I mean taking time off of work, leaving home and doing something to recharge, something enjoyable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Stem Bag (Translated)</title>
      <link>https://misfir3.org/post/stembag-translated/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://misfir3.org/post/stembag-translated/</guid>
      <description>Como Fabricar Tu Propria Bolsa &amp;hellip; Even if you don&amp;rsquo;t speak Spanish!
I came across this video on making a stem bag and tried it out for myself (3 times now). The picture is of the 3rd one, where I feel like I got a pretty good handle on it, but still made some mistakes (as you&amp;rsquo;ll see I also did on my 4th one)
Why This Stem Bag, Why This Post?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bikepacking Hobble L-R</title>
      <link>https://misfir3.org/post/bikepacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://misfir3.org/post/bikepacking/</guid>
      <description>Since I said I&amp;rsquo;d talk about bikepacking some, let me tell you about a recent (not completely successful trip). Before I continue on my summary version, let me tell you a better full version is here.
We had already canceled one planned trip (to the San Rafael well) in late March. We were starting to feel better about local trips (given the pandemic curve etc.), So we headed off. The picture at the top was from the day before the ride when I was doing a test run with the bike loaded (but dry water bottles).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>